<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MarkMartiak</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="about_mark_description">Mark\'s 30-year career spans financial services, media and retail.
        At Premier Wealth Management, he serves individuals and institutional clients, with special focus on the financial planning
        issues related to family offices, divorce, retirement, trust and estate planning. Mark can be seen as a regular guest on CNBC
        and FOX BUSINESS NEWS, and is often quoted in The Wall Street Journal.
</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="string_array_heading">
        <item>The Trump Era begins: Bulls, Bears and Pass on the Fish and Chips (Post BREXIT) for Bagels and Reality TV in D.C.</item>
        <item>Globalization and The Trump Age - Pass the Fish and Chips, Now We are Talking Reality TV</item>
        <item>Dearly Beloved, Prince Rogers Nelson - Enigma Throughout</item>
        <item>Game Changer - Trump’s First 200 Days</item>
        <item>David Bowie Downtown Denizen and Financial Innovator</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_description" formatted="false">
        <item>In the past eight years, pundits have suggested a bear market after a 10% correction but each time,
            the market has bounced back to new highs. One example occurred In 2011, when the S and P 500 fell by 19.4% from April 29th to October 3rd.
            I believe the Q/3/2015 correction was no different. Like many others on Wall Street,
            I was surprised that the recent highs would be achieved on the heels of the Trump
            election victory and be sustained leading up to the President Elect’s inauguration on January 20th, 2017.
            There’s no real definition of a bear market, or a bull market, for that matter.
            Most pundits use the rule-of-thumb that a bear market is a 20% drop from a prior peak.
            However, in 1962 this happened in the midst of a long running rise in stock prices that went on until 1966.
        </item>

        <item>Early during the morning of June 24th,
            news came that Britain voted to leave the European Union aka BREXIT a historic decision certain to reshape the nation’s place in the world,
            disrupt the Continent and rock political establishments throughout the West.j
            Welcome to the TRUMP AGE – the people voted with their raw emotions. The sterling pound dropped to a more than a thirty-year low. Sovereign independence cried-out.
        </item>

        <item>I first heard about the artist named Prince in the late 1970s I wondered to myself who is this cat – and where’s his funk, pop and androgynous sound coming from?
            His music integrated a wide variety of styles, including funk, rock, RandB, soul, psychedelia, and pop.
            Prince reminded me of the modern versions of James Brown, Little Richard, Sly and The Family Stone,
            Carlos Santana and Eric Clapton all rolled-up into one cool multi-talented dude.
        </item>
        <item>\“The stock market has reached record levels since Trump\'s election in anticipation of pro-growth policies\”
            Trump delivered his address to a joint session of Congress on March 2nd after the markets close.
            The U.S. President appeared to be composed and \“presidential\” when he asked Congress to approve a $1 trillion investmen
        </item>
        <item>
            My first Bowie exposure was to Hunky Dory and evolved into listening to Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars while adjusting to
            a new home in a suburban New Jersey town. Assimilating into my new high school, I felt that I had to establish my own identity as a
            person. I found that persona in David Bowie. He made it cool to feel creative and express a hip fashion sense in suburbia.
            In the mid-1970s, one could be categorized as either a \‘Nerd,\’ a \‘Jock\’ or a ‘Head’.
            I wanted to blend the latter two, co-existing among the students, athletes and partiers.
            It was the Bowie connection that gave me my edge.
        </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="string_array_date">
        <item>Wednesday, 01 March 2017 | MARK</item>
        <item>Thursday, 29 April 2017 | MARK</item>
        <item>Saturday, 11 April 2017</item>
        <item>Tuesday, March 28, 2017</item>
        <item>Friday, February 26, 2016</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
